[wings flutter & bird squawks]
[paws thumping]
[insect chirping]
[dogs barking in distance]
[barking intensifies]
[insects chirping]
♪♪[tranquil]
[dogs barking in distance]
[growls]
[all barking]
♪♪[tense]
♪♪[suspenseful]
[dogs barking]
♪♪[fades out]
[bird screams]
[all screaming]
♪♪[uneasy]
[hooves thudding in distance]
♪♪[foreboding]
[rumbling in distance]
♪♪[fades out]
[dog barking]
[branch snaps]
[barks]
[dog barks]
[cat yowls]
[cat mewls]
[barking]
[owl hooting in distance]
[chimes tinkling]
[dog barking]
♪♪[uneasy]
[water sloshes]
[cat mewls]
[barking]
[dog barking]
[dogs barking]
[dog barks]
♪♪[suspenseful]
♪♪[fades out]
♪♪[curious, tense]
[hisses, then snarls]
♪♪[fades out]
[flies buzzing]
[wildlife chirping]
[wood thumping & metal clinking]
[thumping & clinking continue]
♪♪[mysterious]
[lemur chittering]
[lemur screeches]
[screeches]
[mewls]
[birds screaming]
[cat mewls, then yowls]
[squawks]
[mewling]
[screams]
[muffled birdcalls]
[birdcalls fade]
[yowls]
[mewls]
[yowling]
[birds squawk]
[yowls]
[capybara grunts]
[mewls]
-[chitters]
-[grunts]
♪♪[mysterious]
[items clatter]
[screeching]
[items clanking]
[lemur whining]
[capybara grunts]
[cat approaching]
[lemur chittering]
[items clattering]
♪♪[mysterious]
[meows]
[capybara grunts]
[plantains thudding]
♪♪[fades out]
[yawns]
[capybara snoring]
♪♪[solemn]
♪♪[foreboding]
[rumbling in distance]
[yelping]
♪♪[fades out]
[meows]
♪♪[curious]
[water splashes]
[dog barks]
[screeches]
[mewls]
♪♪[fades out]
[squawks]
♪♪[pensive]
[shrilling]
[squawks]
[cat yowls]
[lemur chitters]
[bird squawks]
[squawks]
♪♪[suspenseful]
-[squawking]
-[mewls]
♪♪[dramatic]
[birds squawking]
[squawks]
[shrieking]
♪♪[fades out]
♪♪[melancholy]
[squawks]
[screams]
♪♪[tranquil]
[dog whimpering]
♪♪[fades out]
[whimpers]
[lemur squeaks]
[dog woofing]
[lemur chittering]
[cat yowls]
[items clink]
[squeaks]
[chittering nearby]
♪♪[curious]
[chittering]
[items clanking]
[yowling, hissing]
♪♪[fades out]
[boat thumps]
♪♪[mysterious]
[birds chirping]
♪♪[mysterious, tense]
♪♪[fades out]
[woofs]
[dog approaching]
[chittering, screeching]
[screams]
-[barks]
-[chittering, screeching]
[meows]
[lemur screeching]
[bird screeching]
[yowls]
[mewling]
-[both screeching]
-[dog barking]
[mewling]
[chittering]
♪♪[mysterious]
♪♪[fades out]
[flies buzzing]
-[sneezes]
-[screeches]
[grunts, then snores]
♪♪[whimsical]
[screeching]
[screeches]
[meows]
♪♪[upbeat]
♪♪[fades out]
[paws clicking on floor]
[dog grunts]
[grunts]
[dog whining]
[dog woofs]
[dog barks in distance]
[dogs barking in distance]
[barking]
[dogs barking]
[grunts]
-[barks]
-[grunts]
-[dog barking]
-[capybara grunts]
[meows]
[dog barking]
[dogs barking]
[cat purring]
[screeches]
[cat whimpers]
[whimpers]
-[chitters]
-[barks]
[growls]
[snarls]
[dogs whimper]
[mewls]
[lemur squeaks]
[lemur screeching]
[dogs barking]
[meows]
[squeaks]
[whimpering]
♪♪[eerie]
♪♪[gloomy, dramatic]
[wind howling]
♪♪[fades out]
[mewls]
[wave thuds]
♪♪[soft, pensive]
[squawks]
♪♪[stirring, ethereal]
[meows]
♪♪[tranquil]
[mewls]
♪♪[fades out]
[meows]
[yowls]
[rumbling nearby]
♪♪[mysterious]
♪♪[fades out]
[wildlife chirping]
[meowing]
[mewls]
[chittering in distance]
♪♪[tranquil]
[lemurs chittering]
[squeaks]
[mewls]
♪♪[melancholy]
♪♪[fades out]
[chittering]
♪♪[stirring, hopeful]
[barking]
[all barking]
[branches creaking]
[tree groans]
♪♪[suspenseful]
[chitters]
[barks]
♪♪[fades out]
[dog grunts]
[capybara groans]
-[woofs]
-[meows]
♪♪[tense]
[rumbling in distance]
[barking]
[snuffled breathing]
♪♪[tender]
[dog barks]
♪♪[fades out]
♪♪[stirring]
♪♪[tranquil]
♪♪[fades out]